

Check out My Portfolio

Contact

+212 699 913 184

1 212 099 913 102

.....

in ayad zakaria

https://ayadzakaria.vercel.app

ayadzakaria.pro@gmail.com

Education

 Specialized Technician, Digital Development, Full Stack Option diploma.

2021 - 2023

The Roches Noires Institute of Applied Technology - Casablanca.

Baccalaureate in Earth and Life
Sciences - With honors.

2019 - 2020

Moulay Youssef High School - Sidi Bernoussi.

Skills

TECHNICAL

- HTML, CSS (Bootstrap/Tailwind)
- Node js / Express js
- React js / Alpine js / Vue js
- MySQL / MongoDB
- PHP(Laravel / Livewire)
- Python
- Git/GitLab/GitHub
- Docker / VMs

BEHAVIORAL

- Teamwork
- Problem-solving
- Strong interest in learning new technologies

Ayad Zakaria

Web Developer

About

Hello, I'm Zakaria, a web developer expert with over 2 years of experience. Specializing in native coding, I create professional and personalized web apps. My focus is on delivering high-quality, visually appealing, and user-friendly solutions.

Interests

- Personal project creation
- Participation in hackathons
- Mentoring

Work Experience

Junior web Developer

DigiSystems & Services. (October 2023 - present

• I've been actively involved in developing fully-functional information systems utilizing Tailwind CSS, Alpine JS, Laravel, and Livewire. Additionally, I've contributed to various other websites and created numerous APIs during my tenure.

React Developer (internship-PFE)

DigiMperial (February 2023 - Mars 2023)

 The development of an administration dashboard and a modern mobile apps showcase..

Volunteer Work

Welcome and Orientation Assistant for new registrants

The Roches Noires Institute of Applied Technology Casablanca. (May 2023 - September 2023)

- Information exchanges regarding the field of Digital Development.
- Assisting them in making academic choices and guiding them through the registration process.